If you see a faded sign at the side of the road that says
"15 miles to the Love Shack"
Love Shack, yeah, yeah
I'm headin' down the Atlanta highway
Lookin' for the love getaway
Headed for the love getaway
I got me a car, it's as big as a whale
And we're headin' on down to the Love Shack
I got me a Chrysler, it seats about 20
So hurry up and bring your jukebox money
The love shack is a little old place where we can get together
Love Shack, baby (a-Love Shack, baby)
Love Shack, baby, Love Shack
Sign says (woo) "Stay away, fools"
'Cause love rules at the Love Shack
Well, it's set way back in the middle of a field
Just a funky old shack and I gotta get back
Glitter on the mattress
Glitter on the highway
Glitter on the front porch
The Love Shack is a little old place where we can get together
Love Shack, baby (Love Shack, baby)
Love Shack, that's where it's at
Huggin' and a-kissin'
Dancin' and a-lovin'
Wearin' next to nothin'
'Cause it's hot as an oven
The whole shack shimmies when everybody's
Movin' around and around and around and around
Everybody's movin', everybody's groovin', baby
Folks linin' up outside just to get down
Funky little shack
Funky little shack!
Hop in my Chrysler, it's as big as a whale and it's about to set sail
I got me a car, like, it seats about 20
So come on and bring your jukebox money
The Love Shack is a little old place where we can get together
Love Shack, baby (a-Love Shack, baby)
Love Shack, baby, Love Shack
Bang, bang, bang, on the door, baby
Knock a little louder, sugar
I can't hear you
Bang, bang, bang, on the door, baby
Bang, bang (On the door)
Bang, bang (On the door, baby)
Bang, bang
Your what?
Tin roof, rusted!
Love Shack, baby, Love Shack
Love Shack, baby, Love Shack (Love, baby, that's where it's at, yeah)
Love Shack, baby, Love Shack (Huggin' and a-kissin',
Dancin' and a-lovin'
At the Love Shack)